A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Librarian of Virginia, 1832-2024 Jan
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1827-2007.
  - 1903-1968 (Accession 28078)., 72.45 (212 boxes)
    - A, 1906-1913 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A, 1914-1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - A, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - A-Am, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - A, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - A, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - A, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - A, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - A, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - A, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - A, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - A, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - A, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - A, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - A, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - A, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - A, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - A, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - A-Am, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - An-Ay, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - A, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - A, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - A, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - A, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - A, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - A, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - A, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - A, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - A, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - A, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - A, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - A, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A-Am, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Ar-As, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - A-Ar, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - AS, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - American Library Association-Cataloging and Classification Program, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Aid to the Libraries in War Areas, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Certification, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - American Library Association-Committee Members General, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Barrow, William J., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Belvin, William L., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Buhler, Curtis E., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Canfield, Robert, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Clapp, Vernon, E., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Clift, David H., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Dixson, Nelson, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper Dixson, Nelson, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Frost, Malcolm, H., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Hobbs, Robert B., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Kleins, Frederick S., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Kremer, Alvin, W., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Lewis Harry, F., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Lewis, Harry, F., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Ostvold, Harald, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Poole, Frazier G., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Pratt, Dana F., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Rovelstad, Howard, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - American Library Association-Committee on Paper, Stratton, Burton, L., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - American Library Association-Federal Relations, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - American Library Association-Federal Relations, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association-Federal Relations, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - American Library Association-Federal Relations, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Announcements, 1947-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Convention Bureau, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Exhibits, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Exhibit Committee, Brockmann, Charles, R., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Hotels, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Hotel Reservations, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Local Arrangements, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Post Convention Tour, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference: Treasurer, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Architecture and Building Committee, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Armed Forces Librarian, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Association of American Library Schools, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Association of College and Reference Libraries, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Audio Visual Board and ALA Film Office, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Board of Control Southern Regional Education, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Business and Technology, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: County Regional Library, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Division of Cataloging and Classification, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Division of Libraries for Children and Young People, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Division of Library Education, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Division of Public Libraries., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Council Meeting, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General, Cory, John, Mackenzie, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Ivey, John E., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Lord, Milton, E., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General McDiarmid, E.W., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Menhinick, Howard, K., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General New Members, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Planning Committee, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Planning Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Planning Committee Division and Section (General), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Printing of Program, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Public Library Inquiry-Leigh, Robert D., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: General Public Library Inquiry Symposium, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Hospital Division, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Joint Committee of AlA and Rural Sociological Society, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Joint Committee on Library Service to Labor Groups, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Joint Committee on Library as a Career, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Library Extension Division, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: National Association of State Libraries, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Resolution, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Round Table on Library Science Board, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Serials Round Table, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - American Library Association-Southeastern Regional Conference Programs: Staff Organization Round Table, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - American Library Association-Survey of Library Functions of the States, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - American Library Association-Survey of Library Functions of the States, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - American Library Association-Survey of Library Functions of the States, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - American Library Association-Standards for Library Functions at State Level Summary Draft, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - American Library Association-Two Million Dollar Campaign, 1921-1922 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Archives Manual, 1948-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - B, 1905-1908 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - B, 1909-1911 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - B, 1912-1921 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - B, 1922-1924 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Ba-Br, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - B, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - B, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - B, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - B, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - B, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - B, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - B, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - B, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - B, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - B, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - B, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - B, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - B, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - B, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - B, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - B, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - B, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - B, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - B, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - B, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - B, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - B, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - B, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - B, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - B, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - B, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - B, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - B, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - B, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - B, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - B, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - B, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - B, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - B, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - B, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - B, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - B-Bo, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Br-Bu, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - B, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - B, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - B, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - B, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - B, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - B, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Bell Landon C., 1930-1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Bill of Rights, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Blind, Books for The, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Broadside Bibliography Index Cards (see boxes 13-16 for index cards), undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bryan Collection, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - C, 1903-1912 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - C, 1913-1918 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - C, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS- Alabama-Georgia, 1903-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Georgia-Louisiana, 1903-1968 (Box 14 a)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Louisiana-North Carolina, 1903-1968 (Box 14 b)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-North Carolina, 1903-1968 (Box 15 a)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-North Carolina-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 15 b)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 16 a)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 16 b)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 17 a, Folder 1)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 17 b, Folder 2)
    - BROADSIDE INDEX CARDS-Virginia, 1903-1968 (Box 17 c)
    - C, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - C, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - C, 1924-1925 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - C, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - C, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - C, 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - C-Cl, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Co-Cy, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - C-Ch, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Cl-Cy, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - C-Ch, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Cl-Cy, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - C-Ch, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Cl-Cy, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - C-Ch, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cl-Cy, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - C-Ch, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Cl-Cy, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - C-Cl, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Co-Cy, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - C-Cl, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Co-Cy, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - C-Cl, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Co-Cy, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - C-Ch, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cl-Cy, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - C-Ci, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cl-Cu, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Ca-Cl, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Co-Cu, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - C, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Ca-Cl, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Co-Cu, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Ca-Ch, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Ci-Cu, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ca-Ci, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Ci-Cu, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Ca-Cl, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Co-Cu, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ca-Ci, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Cl-Cu, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ca-Ci, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Cl-Cu, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - C, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - C, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - C, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - C, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - C, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - C, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - C, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - C, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - C, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - C, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - C, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - C, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - C, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - C, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - C, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - C, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - C, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - C-Ch, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Co, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Bus Change Proposal, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Capitol Needs Committee, 1947-1953 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Citizen's Arena Committee, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Citizens's Beautification Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - City Manager, 1952-1954 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - City Manager-The Hartford Times, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - City Council Code, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Express Toll Roads, 1938-1954 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Financial Reports, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Financial Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - General, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - General-Richmond News Leader, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - General, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Housing, 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Mayor, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Memorandum Docket, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Minutes of Council Meetings, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Minutes of Council Meetings, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Ordinances (City), 52-130/52-200, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Ordinances (City), 52-201/52-262, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Ordinances (City), 53-1/53-50, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Ordinances (City), 53-51/53-85, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Ordinance Correspondence, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Parking Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Personal, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Real Estate Assessments, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Reports-Dept. of Recreation City Government and Operations of Cemeteries, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Resolutions (City), 52-R117/53-R15 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Retirement Plans, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Richmond Stadium Authority, 1948-1954 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Sewage Disposal, 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Church, Randolph: City Council - Virginia World War II Memorial Committee, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files-Invoices, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Church, Randolph: Personal Files, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University Bicentennial, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Columbia University Bicentennial Photographs, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Library Salaries, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Preservation, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Conservation of Cultural Resources U.S. World War History, 1941-1942 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Conservation of Cultural Resources United States, 1941-1942 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Conservation of Cultural Resources Virginia, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Council on Library Resources-Application for Grants (Preliminary), 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Council on Library Resources-Articles, 1957-1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Council on Library Resources-Barrows Report, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Council on Library Resources-Barrows Report, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Council on Library Resources-Barrows Report, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Council on Library Resources-Basic Documents, Report, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Council on Library Resources-Conference on Book Paper, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Council on Library Resources-Conference on Book Paper, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Council on Library Resources-Conference on Book Paper, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Council on Library Resources-Consultants General, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Council on Library Resources-Consultants Library, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Council on Library Resources-Consultants (Special), 1957-1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Council on Library Resources-Consultants (Scientific), 1957-1960 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Council on Library Resources-General Announcements, 1956-1960 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Council on Library Resources-General Announcements, 1961-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Council on Library Resources-Herty Foundation, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Council on Library Resources-Literature Research Project, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Council on Library Resources-Miscellaneous, 1957-1965 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Council on Library Resources-Progress Reports and Finances, 1957-1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Council on Library Resources-Proposed Meeting on Paper Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - D, 1904-1910 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - D, 1911-1912 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - D, 1913-1916 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - D, 1917-1920 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - D, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - D, 1922-1923 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - D, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - D, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Da-Di, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Do-Dy, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Da-De, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Di-Dr, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Du, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Da, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Di-Dr, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Do-Du, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Da, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - De-Di, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Do-Dy, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - D-De, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 6)